(Leonard:)How come it's not a party
when we do it here?
(Sheldon:)Because we don't
throw parties.
(Leonard:)I don't know
what to tell you, Sheldon.
(Leonard:)I'm going to see Priya.
Everyone's over there.
(Leonard:)You coming or not?
(Sheldon:)Well, no, sir,
and do you know why?
In a word: tradition.
(Sheldon:)Every Thursday night
for the last eight years,
(Sheldon:)you and I and our friends
have gathered here
(Sheldon:)in this very spot to break bread
covered with cheese and sauce,
(Sheldon:)discuss the issues
of the day,
(Sheldon:)and yes, share a laugh or two.
(Sheldon:)But I guess our rich heritage
means nothing to you.
(Leonard:)I guess you're right.
(Leonard:)- See you later.
- Wait!
(Sheldon:)Leonard! Wait!
(Sheldon:)What am I going
to do for dinner?
(Leonard:)Come with me to Raj's
and eat there.
(Sheldon:)I can't do that.
(Sheldon:)What if he serves haggis
and blood pudding?
(Leonard:)I really doubt
that's what he'll serve.
(Sheldon:)But what if he does?
(Sheldon:)I'll be obliged to dine
(Sheldon:)on liver and lungs stuffed
in a sheep's stomach.
(Sheldon:)And frankly, blood pudding is
essentially the same thing.
(Sheldon:)I don't know why
he's serving both.
(Leonard:)What do you want to do?
(Leonard:)You want to come with me, or
do you want to sit here alone?
(Sheldon:)No, I'll go
to your haggis party.
(Sheldon:)But I'm telling you.
This is adness. This is utter
and complete adness.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪